Zafer OBUZ

Field Service Engineer

GSM : +353 87 3335309 **E-mail** : obuz78@gmail.com

Address: 5 The Way, Dunboyne Castle, Dunboyne

A86 YV83, Meath, Ireland

A highly adaptable and resourceful Field Engineer with extensive experience gained in the aviation sector. A positive and pro-active team player with proven ability to meet deadlines and deliver results. A good communicator, well organised with strong focus on getting the job done on highest quality outcomes. Reliable, self-motivated, problem-solver.

Work Experience

Tokyo Electron Irish Branch - Leixlip / Ireland

(March 2022 - Present)

Field Service Engineer

- Equipment assembly and submodule integration, testing & fault-finding
- Setting up and calibrating semiconductor wafer handling robots
- Robotics teaching and optimization
- Equipment maintenance & service at international customer locations
- Equipment commissioning & test during installation at international customer locations

Lufthansa Technik Shannon Limited Shannon / Ireland (September 2019 – February 2022)

Aircraft Avionic Technician

Turkish Air Force 3rd Main Jet Base / KONYA

(July 2012 - August 2019)

Boeing 737 AEW&C (E-7T) Aircraft Electrical and Environmental System Technician

Turkish Air Force 9th Main Jet Base Line Maintenance Department / BALIKESİR (July 2001- July 2012)

F-16 Aircraft Electrical & Environmental Systems Technician

Professional Training

- ➤ B737-600/700/800/900 (CFM56) For Cat. B1 and B2 OJT Still in Progress Lufthansa Technik Shannon Limited / Shannon, Clare, Ireland
- ▶ B737 NG/AEW&C Avionics Line & Base Maintenance Course Year: 2012 Boeing Training Center Seattle / WA / USA
- > B737 NG / AEW&C Electric & Avionics Line & Base Maintenance OJT Course Year: 2013 3rd Main Jet Base KONYA / TURKEY

Education

Bachelor's Degree Anatolian University / ESKISEHIR / TURKEY Economy

College Degree Erciyes University / KAYSERI / TURKEY Aircraft Electrical Systems

Certificates

EASA Part-66 B1.1 Licence	Dutch Aviation Authority	30 December 2022
B737-600/700/800/900 (CFM56) for Cat. B1 and B2 Theory Elements Certificate	Aviet Limited	January 2021
B737-600/700/800/900 (CFM56) For Cat. B1 and B2 Practical Elements Certificate	Aviet Limited	January 2021

Language Skills

English Reading: Advance, Writing: Advance, Speaking: Advance

Social Activities

Tennis

Computer Skills

Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, Access: Working Knowledge

SAP Source Management System Maintenance and Logistics Module: Working Knowledge